<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Damian Rajca</title>
    <link>https://rajca.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Damian Rajca</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://rajca.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Home Access over VPN</title>
      <link>https://rajca.org/project/vpn-nat/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rajca.org/project/vpn-nat/</guid>
      <description>How to configure access to computer behind NAT Network using OpenVPN. Requirements:  Linux server with root access preferable CentOS 7 Basic bash knowledge  Let&amp;rsquo;s start! Server configuration part Login to our VPN Server ssh root@&amp;lt;server&amp;gt;  Install additional epel repository yum -y install epel-release  Make some updates yum -y update &amp;amp;&amp;amp; yum -y upgrade  Stop firewalld systemctl stop firwalld  Disable firwalld systemctl disable firwalld  Start iptables systemctl start iptables  Enable iptables systemctl enable iptables   Now we have needed iptables up and running for further access controlling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home Lab access over VPN</title>
      <link>https://rajca.org/post/vpn-nat/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rajca.org/post/vpn-nat/</guid>
      <description>Hi! It&amp;rsquo;s going to be my first real blog post! I&amp;rsquo;m going to start from something technical, quite useful in developers world. From time to time I faced some problems with connecting to my lab, located in my flat. The situation is because my internet provider uses NAT network. It&amp;rsquo;s not easy to get access to this network for example over SSH. There are some options, for example team viewer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>hello</title>
      <link>https://rajca.org/post/hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2017 11:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rajca.org/post/hello/</guid>
      <description>Hello everyone, this is a test post!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>